Ma The Thanh - Frontend Developer

Phone: +843 7621.9276 / Email: thanhmtfpt@gmail.com / Linkedin: thanhmathe / Portfolio

SUMMARY

I'm a Full Stack Software Engineer with 4 years of experience in Web Development. I have over 3 years of experience in Modern Front-End Web Development and 1 year of PHP-related technologies.

With my knowledge of UI/UX design, I enjoy solving front-end problems and creating the best user experience for users. I also learn new technologies and best practices to become a better engineer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript, PHP

Frameworks/ Platforms:

- ReactJS, NodeJS, Webpack/Babel
- jQuery, Tailwind, MaterialUI, Bootstrap
- MVC, Web API

Database Management Systems: MS SQL Server, My SQL, Non-SQL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

J&T Express - Full Stack Developer Project:

11/2021 - Now

- * banhang.upos.vn (8 members, 6 front-end, 2 back-ends) Front-end Developer:
 - Account: usertest1 usertest1
 - **Description:** A web app sales website for businesses and shop owners with a full range of operations such as product management, warehouse, order journey, customer management, etc...
 - **Technologies:** ReactJS, Webpack, ES6, ESLint, Codeigniter.
 - Responsibilities:
 - _ Invoke in an Agile team which requires joining every meeting and processes
 - _ Pick up user stories, analyze, design, discuss with the team to tackle them, and write documentation to clarify the work.
 - _ Do peer review to help teammates improve code quality and check the correction of dependencies and the system.
- * evoshop.vn (6 members, 4 front-end, 2 back-ends) Front-end Developer:
 - Account: usertest1 usertest1
 - **Description:** Website serving J&T Express shipping unit to manage orders and place orders in bulk.
 - **Technologies:** ReactJS, Webpack, ES6, ESLint, Codeigniter.
 - Responsibilities:

- _ Pick up user stories, analyze, design, discuss with the team to tackle them, and write documentation to clarify the work.
- _ Work closely with customers to clear and resolve requirements.
- Remotely work during COVID-19
- * Portfolio: 1 member Front-end Developer:
 - Technologies: ReactJS, Tailwind, ES6, ESLint, Codeigniter.
- * CRM (2 members, 1 team leader, 1 full-stack) Full-stack Developer:
 - **Description:** A web that helps stakeholders manage all your company's relationships and interactions with customers and prospects.
 - **Technologies:** Laravel, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase.
 - Responsibilities:
 - _ Design UX/UI and implement additional functionalities (both back-end and front-end) based on stakeholders' requirements.
 - _ Design database schema and implement back-end services for the UPOS
 - _ Collaborate with the team leader to define and improve the team's workflow

TechUp Company - Front-end Developer

11/2020 - 11/2021

- * happyskin.vn (6 members, 4 front-end, 2 back-ends) Front-end Developer:
 - **Description:** Conducted a project outsourcing for a beauty products company
 - Technologies: ¡Query, Bootstrap, Firebase, NodeJS.
 - Responsibilities:
 - _ Invoke in Agile Scrum software development process.
 - _ Giving estimation to the item on the product roadmap, turning them into actionable work ticket
 - _ Implement essential sections of the front-end application.

Freelancer 04/2020 - 11/2020

- * Project:
 - Web ReactJS Clone (1 member)
 - o COVID Tracker, Airbnb Clone, Amazon Clone, Netflix Clone

SaiGonTech University - Full-stack Intern

06/2019 - 04/2020

* **Project**: Web <u>Library</u> (4 members)

EDUCATION

SaiGonTech: 10/2018 - 05/2021Studied software engineer